EduWork DataBridge
Blueprint-complete v0.14.0 reference release
SYNTHETIC DEMO · NO COMPANY DATA OR OUTCOME CLAIM
Connect fragmented systems
HRIS · LMS · CRM · assessment · credential · workforce data
Read-only connectors · bounded retries · safe files and networks
Preserve original evidence
Immutable snapshots · SHA-256 · manifests · cursors · resume
Identical content is reused—never silently overwritten
Make data quality inspectable
Masked profiles · approved baselines · drift · bounded mappings
Eight validation categories · quarantine and resolution history
Review identity links responsibly
Trusted IDs first · probabilistic evidence second
Auto-match · gray-zone review · no-match · conflict veto
Publish governed data products
Training · credential · quality marts
Documented fields · masking · lineage · checksums · retention
Operate with evidence
Assets · partitions · retries · watermarks · backfills
Safe telemetry · identity · permissions · audit events
Verify the release
Tests · coverage · benchmark · SBOMs · packages · checksums
Every claim tied to reproducible evidence and limitations
Ready for bounded evaluation
Configure one real workflow · preserve first-hand partner evidence
Pre-production until target-environment and partner checks pass